Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Los Angeles Daily News -- Officials amd Employees -- Portraits., 8 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Daily News -- Views., 5 items (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles River., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles --Views (Hotels). (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Agriculture)., 5 items (Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Aqueduct)., 30 items (Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Ballona Creek)., 1 item (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Buildings) folder 1 of 2., 39 items (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Buildings) folder 2 of 2., 33 items (Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Business enterprises)., 66 items (Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Cemetaries)., 1 item (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Century City)., 4 items (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Chamber of Commerce)., 12 items (Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (China Town)., 31 items (Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Churches)., 41 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Chutes Park)., 7 items (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Civic Center)., 43 items (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Clubs)., 14 items (Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Coliseum)., 3 items (Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Dept. of Water and Power)., 13 items (Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Echo Park)., 5 items (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Elysian Park)., 10 items (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Exposition Park)., 19 items (Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Festivals)., 38 items (Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Floods)., 56 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Fort Hill)., 3 items (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Fort Moore)., 8 items (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Freeways)., 18 items (Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Harbor). Folder 1 of 2., 66 items (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Harbor). Folder 2 of 2. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Hazard's Pavilion)., 5 items (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Hollenbeck Park)., 7 items (Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Hospitals)., 24 items (Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Hotels)., 37 items (Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Lafayette Park)., 4 items (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Lincoln Park)., 26 items (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Los Angeles County Museum of Natural History)., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Los Angeles High School). Folder 1. Views of the building., 16 items (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Los Angeles High School). Folder 2. Class of 1890., 22 items (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Los Angeles School Library Association)., 2 items (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Los Angeles Terminal Railroad)., 22 items (Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Mac Arthur Park)., 39 items (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Maps)., 14 items (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Nineteenth Century)., 37 items (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Oil Wells)., 8 items (Folder 12)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Ostrich Farms)., 6 items (Folder 13)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Palomar Ballroom)., 11 items (Folder 14)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Parks)., 18 items (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Pershing Square)., 24 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Pigeon Farm)., 5 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Plaza)., 51 items (Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Police Department)., 4 items (Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Post Office)., 16 items (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Produce Market)., 1 item (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Public Library), 5 items (Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Railroad Stations)., 36 items (Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Residences) Folder 1 of 4., 38 items (Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Residences) Folder 2 of 4., 29 items (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Residences) Folder 3 of 4., 32 items (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Residences) Folder 4 of 4., 43 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Round House)., 11 items (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Scenic Views)., 9 items (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Schools)., 35 items (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Sketches)., 18 items (Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Skyline)., 21 items (Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Sonoratown)., 4 items (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Southwest Museum)., 1 item (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Sports)., 1 item (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Adams)., 11 items (Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Alameda Street)., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Aliso Street)., 11 items (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Broadway)., 44 items (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Cahuenga Pass)., 3 items (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Chester Place)., 2 items (Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Commercial Street)., 3 items (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Figueroa)., 9 items (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - First Street)., 9 items (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Fourth Street)., 6 items (Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Hill Street)., 5 items (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Hope Street)., 1 item (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Los Angeles Street)., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Main Street)., 54 items (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Mercantile Place)., 3 items (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Mulholland Drive)., 31 items (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - New High Street)., 1 item (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Olvera Street)., 20 items (Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - San Fernando Road)., 2 items (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - San Pedro Street)., 1 item (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Santa Monica Blvd.), 2 items (Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Sixth Street)., 4 items (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Spring Street)., 27 items (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Sunset Blvd.), 7 items (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Temple Street)., 4 items (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Third Street)., 6 items (Folder 17)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Ventura Blvd.), 1 item (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Streets)., 52 items (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Theaters)., 24 items (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Transportation) Folder 1 of 2., 36 items (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Transportation) Folder 2 of 2., 9 items (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Truesdale Estates)., 4 items (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (U.S. Veterans Administration Center)., 82 items (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Vigilance Committee, 1862)., 1 item (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Washington Gardens)., 3 items (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Water Supply)., 10 items (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views (Watts Towers)., 18 items (Folder 1)
- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Views., 24 items (Folder 2)
- Los Gatos, Calif. -- Views., 19 items (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Los Olivos, Santa Barbara Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Loud-Speakers -- Views., 2 items (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Louisiana -- Views., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Loveland, Colo. -- Views., 33 items (Folder 9)
- Lover, Samuel, 1797-1868., 1 items (Folder 10)
- Lowe, T.S.C., 4 items (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Lubin, Isador, 1896-1978, 1 item (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Luce, Clare (Boothe), 1903-1987, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Lugo Family -- Portrait., 25 items (Folder 14)
- Lumbering - California -- Views., 2 items (Folder 11)
- Lumbering -- California., 22 items (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Lummis, Charles Fletcher, 1859-1928., 2 items (Folder 16)
- Lurye, William, d. 1949, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Lyell, Sir Charles, 1st baronet, 1797-1875., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Lyons, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer-Lytton, 1st baron of, 1803-1873., 4 items (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Lytton, Edward Robert Bulwer-Lytton, 1st earl of, 1831-1891., 2 items (Box 40, Folder 20)
- MacDonald, George, 1824-1905., 4 items (Folder 26)
- MacDowell, Edward Alexander, 1861-1908., 2 items (Folder 27)
- Machado Family -- Portrait., 18 items (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Machebeuf, Joseph P., 1 item (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Machen, Arthur, 1863-1947., 30 items (Folder 3)
- Machinery., 42 items (Folder 4)
- Maclay, Charles, 1821-1890., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Macy, John Albert, 1877-1932, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Madison, James, Pres. U.S., 1751-1836., 3 items (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Magdalena, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 18)
- Maginot Line -- Views. (Folder 3)
- Malraux, Andr?, 1901-1976, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Mammoth Lakes, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Manchuria (China)., 31 items (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Manila (Philippines) - Botica Boie (German Dispensary)., 9 items (Folder 23)
- Manila (Philippines) - Manila Hotel., 6 items (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Manila (Philippines)., 13 items (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Manitou Springs, Colo. -- Views., 93 items (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955., 4 items (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Mansfeldt, Hugo -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Mansfield, Katherine, 1888-1923, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Manuzio, Aldo Pio, 1449 or 1450-1515, -- Views., 2 items (Folder 29)
- Marconi, Guglielmo, 1874-1937, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Maritain, Jacques, 1882-1973, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Markham, Edwin, 1852-1940., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Markova, Alicia, 1910-2004., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Marks, Saul, 1905-1975, printer -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Marryat, Frederick, 1792-1848, -- Portrait. (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Marryat, Frederick, 1792-1848, -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Marryat, Frederick, 1792-1848, -- Views., 20 items (Folder 7)
- Marsh, Elmer F., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Marshall, James Wilson., 2 items (Folder 9)
- Marshall, Thomas R., 1854-1925., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Martin, Sir Theodore, 1816-1909., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Martine, Julie Edgar (Rodman)., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Martineau, Harriet, 1802-1876., 3 items (Folder 13)
- Martineau, James 1805-1900., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Martinez Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Marysville, Califor. -- Views., 6 items (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Massachusetts -- Views., 22 items (Folder 17)
- Mathews, J.B., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Matilija Canyon., 6 items (Folder 19)
- Maubant -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Maugham, William Somerset, 1874-1965, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Maurice, Frederick Denison, 1805-1872., 3 items (Folder 22)
- Mazzini, Giuseppe, 1805-1872., 1 item (Folder 23)
- McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1863-1941., 1 item (Folder 21)
- McCain, John Sidney, 1884-1945, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 22)
- McClellan, George Brinton, 1826-1885., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 23)
- McClellan, Mount, Colo. -- Views, 1 item (Folder 24)
- McCook, Alexander McDowell, 1831-1903., 1 item (Folder 25)
- McElvy, Carl C. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 28)
- McFee, William., 1 item (Box 40, Folder 29)
- McGill, Nev. -- Views., 16 items (Box 40, Folder 30)
- McGroarty, John Steven, 1862-1944, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 31)
- McGuire, F.J., 1 item (Folder 32)
- McIntyre, J. Francis A., Archbishop -- Portrait., 6 items (Folder 5)
- McKeeby, G.L., 1 item (Box 41, Folder 6)
- McKinely, Mount -- Views., 2 items (Box 41, Folder 8)
- McKinley, William, Pres. U.S., 1843-1901., 11 items (Folder 7)
- McManus, George, 1884-1954. (Folder 3)
- McManus, George, 1884-1954., 22 items (Folder 10)
- McMichael, Charles Barnsley, 1850- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 41, Folder 11)
- McNair, Lesley James, 1883-1944., 1 item (Box 41, Folder 12)
- McNutt, Paul Vories, 1891-1955., 1 item (Folder 13)
- McPherson, Aimee Semple, 1890-1944, -- Portraits., 5 items (Folder 14)
- McPherson, Aimee Semple. (Folder 5)
- McWilliams, Wilson Carey, 1933-2005, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Meadow Valley, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Meek, Joseph Lafayette, 1810-1875., 3 items (Folder 25)
- Meissen, Ger., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Melchior, Lauritz Lebrecht Hommel, 1890-1973., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Mellus, Francis, 1838-1863, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Mellus, Henry, 1815-1860, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Melones, Calif., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Membreno, Alberto, 1859-1921., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880-1956, -- Portrait., 4 item (Folder 32)
- Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847., 2 items (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Mendocino County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Mercantile buildings., 14 items (Folder 35)
- Merced, Calif. -- Views., 27 items (Folder 36)
- Mergenthaler, Ottmar, 1854-1899, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 37)
- Mesa Verde National Park., 49 items (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Metro Pictures Corp. -- Views., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Mexican-American Border Region., 4 items (Folder 40)
- Miami (Fla.) -- Views., 10 items (Folder 41)
- Micheltorena, Emanuel, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Military Art and Science -- Views., 4 items (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Mill City, Nevada -- Views., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Mill, John Stuart., 1 item (Folder 46)
- Millais, Sir John Everett, 1st bart., 1829-1896., 1 item (Folder 45)
- Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1892-1950, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 47)
- Miller, Henry., 1 item (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Miller, Joaquin, 1841?-1913., 1 item (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Millerton., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Mills College, Oakland, Calif. -- Views., 57 items (Folder 5)
- Mills, Benjamin Fay, 1857-1916., 6 items (Folder 3)
- Mills, Charles W., 1 item (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Miners -- Views., 3 items (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Mines & Mineral Resources -- Arizona., 4 items (Folder 7)
- Mines & Mineral Resources -- California., 21 items (Folder 8)
- Minneapolis -- Views., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Minnesota -- Views., 2 items (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Mint Canyon (Calif.) -- Views., 4 items (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Miramar, San Diego Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Mission Play -- Views., 10 items (Folder 15)
- Missions -- Arizona -- San Jose de Tumacacori., 11 items (Folder 13)
- Missions -- Arizona -- San Xavier., 14 items (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Missions -- California -- La Purisima Concepcion., 44 items (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Missions -- California -- Nuestra Senora de Los Angeles., 18 items (Folder 19)
- Missions -- California -- Nuestra Senora Dolorsisma Soledad., 22 items (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Missions -- California -- San Antonio de Padua., 47 items (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Missions -- California -- San Antonio de Pala., 49 items (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Missions -- California -- San Buenaventura., 27 items (Folder 1)
- Missions -- California -- San Carlos Borromeo., 58 items (Folder 2)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego -- Views., 60 items (Folder 3)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Bells -- Views., 18 items (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Doorways -- Views., 20 items (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Grounds -- Views., 42 items (Folder 6)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Model -- Views., 12 items (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Old Bell Tower -- Views., 10 items (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Old Mission Dam & Acqueduct -- Views., 55 items (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Reconstruction -- Views., 36 items (Folder 10)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Ruins -- Facade -- Views., 44 items (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Ruins -- Interior -- Views., 8 items (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Ruins -- Views., 23 items (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Missions -- California -- San Diego de Alcala -- Sketches -- Views., 10 items (Folder 2)
- Missions - California - San Fernando Rey de Espana. (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Missions -- California -- San Fernando Rey de Espa?a. Folder 1 of 2., 30 items (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Missions -- California -- San Fernando Rey de Espa?a. Folder 1 of 2., 65 items (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Missions -- California -- San Francisco de Assisi., 28 items (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Missions -- California -- San Francisco de Solano., 14 items (Folder 6)
- Missions -- California -- San Gabriel. Folder 1 of 2., 68 items (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Missions -- California -- San Gabriel. Folder 1 of 2., 59 items (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Missions -- California -- San Jose de Guadalupe., 15 items (Folder 1)
- Missions -- California -- San Juan Bautista., 34 items (Folder 2)
- Missions - California - San Juan Capistrano. (Folder 6)
- Missions -- California -- San Juan Capistrano. Folder 1 of 3., 61 items (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Missions -- California -- San Juan Capistrano. Folder 2 of 3., 75 items (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Missions -- California -- San Juan Capistrano. Folder 3 of 3., 67 items (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Missions -- California -- San Luis Obispo., 23 items (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Missions - California - San Luis Rey. (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Missions -- California -- San Luis Rey. Folder 1 of 2., 57 items (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Missions -- California -- San Luis Rey. Folder 2 of 2., 62 items (Folder 1)
- Missions -- California -- San Miguel., 49 items (Folder 2)
- Missions -- California -- San Raphael Archangel., 9 items (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Barbara. Folder 1 of 2., 81 items (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Barbara. Folder 2 of 2., 32 items (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Clara., 12 items (Folder 6)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Cruz., 10 items (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Ines., 35 items (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Missions -- California -- Santa Margarita., 10 items (Folder 9)
- Missions -- California., 41 items (Folder 16)
- Missoula River -- Views., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Mitchell, Margaret, 1900-1949, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Mitropoulos, Dimitri, 1893-1960., 1 item (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Modesto, Calif. -- Views., 23 items (Folder 13)
- Modigliani, Amadeo, 1884-1920., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Modoc County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Moencopi, Arizona -- Views., 4 items (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Mogollon, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Mohawk, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Mojave Desert., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Mojave, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 4)
- Mokelumne Hill, Calif., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Molina, Gloria., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Moltke, Helmuth., 2 items (Folder 9)
- Monaco -- Views., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Monasteries -- Views., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Monk, Henry., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Mono Craters., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Mono Lake, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Monroe, James, Pres. U.S., 1758-1831., 2 items (Folder 15)
- Monroe, La. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Monrovia., 50 items (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Montana -- Views. (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Montana -- Views., 19 items (Folder 18)
- Monte Carlo -- Views., 7 items (Folder 19)
- Monterey -- Views. Folder 1 of 2., 112 items (Folder 20)
- Monterey -- Views. Folder 2 of 2., 64 items (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Monteux, Pierre, 1875-, 1 item (Folder 22)
- Montezuma, N.M. -- Views., 12 items (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Montrose, California., 2 items (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Montrose, Colo. -- Views., 21 items (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Moore, Ernest Carroll, 1871-1955., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Moosa., 4 items (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Morgan, Charles, 1894-1958, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Morgan, Sydney (Owenson) lady, 1783?-1857, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 29)
- Morgenthau, Henry, 1891-1945., 1 item (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Morley, Christopher D., 2 items (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Morris, William, 1834-1896, -- Portrait. (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Morrison, Murray, 1820-1871., 2 items (Folder 2)
- Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872., 2 items (Folder 3)
- Mortensen, William, Mabel Ballin [Los Angeles(?) ca. 193-]., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Moscow -- Views., 18 items (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Moss Landing, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Motor Boats -- Views., 9 items (Folder 7)
- Motorcycles -- Views., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Mott, John Griffin., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Mount Helix -- Views., 6 items (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Mount Lowe -- Views. (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Mount Lowe -- Views., 64 items (Folder 11)
- Mount Rainier National Park -- Views., 6 items (Folder 12)
- Mount St. Mary's College, Los Angeles -- Views., 5 items (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Mount Wilson., 14 items (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Mountainair, N.M. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 15)
- Mountains -- Views., 15 items (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 1 of 7) (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 2 of 7) (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 3 of 7) (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 4 of 7) (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 5 of 7) (Folder 5)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 6 of 7) (Folder 6)
- Mountains -- Views. (folder 7 of 7) (Folder 7)
- Mowry, Sylvester., 1 item (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791., 2 item (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Mueller, Maria -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Muir Woods National Monument., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Muir, John, 1838-1914., 7 items (Folder 20)
- Mulholland, William., 4 items (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Murfreesboro, Battle of, 1862-1863., 8 items (Box 50, Folder 1)
  ALSO SHELVED IN PHOTO 99 DRAWER, MAP ROOM
- Murman, Eugene Otto Walter, 1874-1962, -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Murray, Gilbert, 1866-1957., 1 item (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Murray, Neil Randall, 1889-1959., 2 items (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Murray, Wellwood., 1 item (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Murrietta, Calif. -- Views., 30 items (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Murrietta, Juaquin, 1829-1853, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Muybridge, Eadweard, 1830-1904, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Nadeau, Remi -- Portrait., 13 items (Folder 9)
- Nance, Frank -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Napa County, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Napa, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 11)
- Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1769-1821, -- Portrait., 5 items (Folder 13)
- Naranjo, Alberto C. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Nathan, Robert, 1894-1985., 4 items (Box 50, Folder 15)
- National City, Calif. -- Views., 14 items (Box 50, Folder 16)
- National Parks -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Folder 6)
- National Parks -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 4)
- National Parks and Reserves., 18 items (Folder 18)